let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
        option: [
            "yes",
            "No",
            "machine dependent",
            "none of the mentioned",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier?",
        option: [
            "31 characters",
            " 63 characters",
            " 79 characters",
            " none of the mentioned",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is invalid?",
        option: [
            "_a = 1",
            "__a = 1",
            "__str__ = 1",
            "none of the mentioned",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which of the following is an invalid variable?",
        option: [
            "my_string_1",
            "1st_string",
            "foo",
            "_",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which of the following is not a keyword?",
        option: [
            "eval",
            "assert",
            "nonlocal",
            "pass",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "All keywords in Python are in _________",
        option: ["lower case",
                  "UPPER CASE",
                   "Capitalized",
                   "None of the mentioned"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
        option: [
            "abc = 1,000,000",
            "a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
            "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
            "a_b_c = 1,000,000",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            ". What is the output of print 0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3?",
        option: ["True", "False", "Machine dependent", "Error"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a Python tuple?",
        option: ["[1, 2, 3]", "(1, 2, 3)", "{1,2,3}", "{}"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following statements create a dictionary?",
        option: ["d = {}", "d = {“john”:40, “peter”:45}", "d = {40:”john”, 45:”peter”}", "All of the mentioned"],
        answer: 4,
    },
];
